culture11.com 2008-12-18

# Privacy Policy | Culture11

Your privacy is our priority. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or want to better understand the controls you as a Culture11 member, have in our community, please e-mail our Privacy Director at [privacy.director@Culture11.com](mailto:privacy.director@Culture11.com).

### Privacy Policy Updates

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, Culture11 may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, Culture11 will post our updated Privacy Policy on the Site located at the following URL: [http://www.privacypolicy.Culture11.com](http://culture11.com/privacypolicy "www.privacypolicy.Culture11.com"), and will post notice of the change so it is visible when members log on for the first time after the change is posted. Culture11 may also send registered users of the Culture11.com (the "Site") e-mail notifications notifying such users of any changes to the Privacy Policy. Culture11 encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Site and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.

### Information Collection and Use

To use certain services on this Site, we ask that you register for an account and we may invite you to submit questions, comments or request information. Due to the nature of some of these activities, we also ask you to complete and submit an online registration form with personally identifiable information including, but not limited to, username and geographic location. Culture11 may also collect other personally identifiable information in order to assist users in communicating and interacting with each other and to suggest relevant content and advertising. We may use your personally identifiable information to provide you with passwords and deliver certain services or information you have requested, recommend content, verify your authority to enter certain password-protected areas of the Site, send you notices for services that may be of interest to you (if you have opted to receive such notices) and improve the content and general administration of the Site. User profile information, including users' pictures and usernames, may be displayed to other users of the Site in order to facilitate user interaction in the Culture11 online community. Your full name is never directly revealed to other users without your express permission, unless you include your full name in your user profile, blog or as your username. To facilitate searching and finding other friends on the Site, Culture11 allows users to search for other users by only the uniquely identifiable information that the user has made public on the Site.

### Invitations and Other Communications to Non-Members

Culture11 users are encouraged to invite friends to join the Site and register for the services by sending e-mail invitations via an automated invitation system or other delivery method. Culture11 stores the e-mail addresses or other user data that users provide so that the respondents may be added to the inviter's list of friends on its personal page and also to send e-mail reminders to invitees who have not responded. Culture11 does not sell these e-mail addresses or other user information or use them to send any other communications other than invitations, invitation reminders.

### Children's Privacy

Culture11 recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. Culture11's services and the Site are not intended for children under the age of 13. Culture11 does not target its services or this Site to children under 13. Culture11 does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

### Cookies

We may use small text files called cookies to improve overall Site experience, including, but not limited to, the purposes of ensuring that users are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize advertising and Web page content based on browser type, computer operating system and user profile information. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you but some cookies may include personally identifiable information. Cookies must be enabled for you to use certain areas of the Site. Culture11 may allow third party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on the Site to set and access their cookies on your computer. Third party advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the Culture11 Privacy Policy.

### Aggregate Information

The Site may track aggregated data about its users in order to determine the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, IP addresses, External Web Sites (defined below) linked to, and other relevant data. We may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be used in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movement, target advertising and promotions and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

### Disclosure

We may provide your personally identifiable information that we collect and the data generated by cookies to the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us and to third party partner entities that are not within the Culture11 corporate family. For example, we may provide your personally identifiable information to an organization in order to complete a service (e.g., process your payment) or to third parties to send you information about products and/or services. Such third party entities may be obligated to protect your personally identifiable information consistent with the terms of this Privacy Policy. We will also disclose your personally identifiable information (a) if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority, (b) to enforce the Culture11 Terms of Use agreement or to protect our rights or (c) to protect the safety of users of the Site and its services.

### Comment Threads, Blogs, Message Boards, Classifieds and Other Public Areas

Whenever you voluntarily post public information to comment threads, blogs, message boards, classifieds or other public areas, such information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

### Third Party Advertising

Ads appearing on this Site will be delivered to you by Culture11 and/or one of its Web advertising or sponsorship partners. Culture11 and its Web advertising and sponsorship partners may set cookies that allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. Ad servers, therefore, may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads were clicked on. This information allows Culture11 and its advertising partners and ad network to deliver targeted ads and information that they believe will be of the most interest to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third party advertisers.

### Email Opt-Out

Users who no longer wish to receive notifications may choose not to by opting out through a reply e-mail or modifying their user preferences when available.

### Links to Third Party Sites

The Site may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which Culture11 does not have control ("External Web Sites"). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Culture11 of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that Culture11 is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that Culture11 is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites.

### Security

We may employ procedural and technological measures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, such as securing accounts with user-created passwords and restricting access to user information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions. Such measures are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

### Correcting/Updating Personally Identifiable Information

Culture11 provides you with the ability to review, correct and delete any of the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us your user profile, but you should understand that this does not necessarily give you the ability to delete any content and/or material that you have posted to the Site, including, without limitation, blogs, videos, audio and/or pictures, that is posted in areas other than your user profile. Once we have deleted or removed your user profile, you agree that Culture11 shall not be responsible for any personally identifiable information that was not included within your deleted and/or removed user profile that remains on the Site. If you wish to review or correct any information you have provided to us, you may access your account and review, correct and delete your personally identifiable information or you may contact us by e-mail at: [privacy.director@Culture11.com](mailto:privacy.director@Culture11.com). Upon your written request, we will remove any personally identifiable information as requested as soon as reasonably possible.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us via email at: [privacy.director@Culture11.com](mailto:privacy.director@Culture11.com).
